<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CheckMySelf</string>
    <string name="you_cancel_location_permission">You canceled location permission</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="create_an_account">Create an Account</string>
    <string name="your_health_vitals_at_your_fingertips">Your health vitals at your fingertips</string>
    <string name="please_wait">Please wait…</string>
    <string name="no_internet_connection">No internet connection, Please try again</string>
    <string name="error_message_no_network">You are not currently connected to the internet.\n Please try again when you get online.</string>
    <string name="retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading…</string>
    <string name="no_result_found">No Result Found</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="forgot_password_que">Forgot Password?</string>
    <string name="dont_have_account">Don\'t have an Account? Sign Up</string>
    <string name="email_not_found_msg">Couldn\'t find this email address in our records</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="incorrect_password">Incorrect Password</string>
    <string name="pls_enter_email">Please enter email</string>
    <string name="pls_enter_valid_email">Please enter valid email</string>
    <string name="pls_enter_password">Please enter password</string>
    <string name="check_my_self_copy_right">CheckMySelf © 2023</string>
    <string name="tutorial_0_title">Measure your vital signs</string>
    <string name="tutorial_0_message">Look at the front-facing (Selfie) camera or place your finger over the rear-facing camera.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_1_title">How to use face measurement</string>
    <string name="tutorial_1_message">For best results, try to place the device on a stand an arm\'s length away from your face.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_2_title">How to use face measurement</string>
    <string name="tutorial_2_message">Make sure there is no light source behind you - only in front of you. Look straight into the camera.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_3_title">How to use finger measurement</string>
    <string name="tutorial_3_message">Sit comfortably. Place your index finger on the camera, applying moderate pressure.</string>
    <string name="tutorial_4_title">How to use finger measurement</string>
    <string name="tutorial_4_message">Make sure that your finger completely covers the relevant rear camera. Do not cover the flashlight.</string>
    <string name="get_started">Get Started</string>
    <string name="first_name">First Name</string>
    <string name="last_name">Last Name</string>
    <string name="email_address">Email Address</string>
    <string name="get_otp">Get OTP</string>
    <string name="forgot_password_msg">Please enter your registered email address and we will send you  the OTP (One Time Password).</string>
    <string name="reset_password">Reset Password</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>
    <string name="already_have_account">Already Have an Account? Log In</string>
    <string name="please_select_dob">Please select date of birth</string>
    <string name="date_of_birth">Date of Birth</string>
    <string name="please_select_gender">Please select gender</string>
    <string name="weight_in_kg">Weight (in kgs)</string>
    <string name="height_in_cms">Height (in cms)</string>
    <string name="pls_enter_first_name">Please enter first name</string>
    <string name="male">Male</string>
    <string name="female">Female</string>
    <string name="other">Other</string>
    <string name="select_gender">Select Gender</string>
    <string name="enter_a_strong_password">Enter a strong password</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="confirm_password">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="password_didnt_match_the_guidelines">Password didn\'t match the guidelines</string>
    <string name="password_didnt_match">Password didn\'t match</string>
    <string name="pls_enter_weight">Please enter weight</string>
    <string name="pls_enter_height">Please enter height</string>
    <string name="password_guidelines">Password Guidelines:</string>
    <string name="password_guideline_1">Must have 1 uppercase letter and 1 special character (!@#$%^&amp;).</string>
    <string name="password_guideline_2">Must have at least 8 but not exceed 20 alphanumeric characters.</string>
    <string name="password_guideline_3">Must not contain spaces.</string>
    <string name="enter_activation_code">Enter activation code</string>
    <string name="activation_code_sent_on_email_msg">Please enter the activation code sent  to your email address.</string>
    <string name="activate">Activate</string>
    <string name="resend_activation_code">Resend Activation Code</string>
    <string name="before_getting_started">Before getting started</string>
    <string name="continue_">Continue</string>
    <string name="before_started_msg">This App is NOT a medical or diagnostic product.\n\nMeasurements provided by this application are intended for informational purposes only and aim to promote general wellness.\n\nThe measured indicators are not intended for medical purposes; they are designed only for general fitness and wellness.\n\nYour data and measurements will be stored and processed by the App.</string>
    <string name="term_check_full_text">I have read and agree to the Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="term_of_use">Terms of Use</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="hello">Hello</string>
    <string name="you_are_registered_now">You‘re now a registered user!</string>
    <string name="enter_otp">Enter OTP</string>
    <string name="otp_code_sent_on_email_msg">Please enter the OTP sent to your registered email address.</string>
    <string name="didnt_received_otp">Didn\'t received the OTP?</string>
    <string name="resend">Resend</string>
    <string name="create_a_new_password">Create a new password</string>
    <string name="create_password">Create Password</string>
    <string name="your_password_has_been_reset">Your password has been successfully reset!</string>
    <string name="you_can_now_use_new_password">You can now use your new password to log in to your account.</string>
    <string name="return_to_login">Return to Login</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure_want_to_logout">Are you sure want to logout?</string>
    <string name="done">Done</string>
    <string name="health_history">Health History</string>
    <string name="about_the_app">About the App</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="view_profile">View Profile</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="health_scan">Health Scan</string>
    <string name="profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="your_bmi">Your BMI</string>
    <string name="your_category">Your Category</string>
    <string name="save_changes">Save Changes</string>
    <string name="app_walk_through">App Walkthrough</string>
    <string name="send_feedback">Send Feedback</string>
    <string name="terms_of_service">Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="got_it">Got it</string>
    <string name="face_option_select_title">%s, ready to measure your vital signs?</string>
    <string name="face_option_select_msg">Sit still, ensure your face is evenly illuminated and there is no light source behind you.</string>
    <string name="finger_option_select_title">Place your finger on the rear camera (not on the selfie camera).</string>
    <string name="finger_option_select_msg">Place your finger on the camera\n(not the flashlight), applying moderate pressure. Click Measure Now.</string>
    <string name="measure_now">Measure Now</string>
    <string name="face">Face</string>
    <string name="finger">Finger</string>
    <string name="delete_account">Delete Account</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure_want_to_delete_account">Are you sure want to delete account?</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="app_version">App Version</string>
    <string name="sdk_version">SDK Version</string>
    <string name="about_app_link_text">For more information on CheckMySelf visit us at: https://CheckMySelf/app</string>
    <string name="no_measurement_were_taken">No measurements were\ntaken on this date</string>
    <string name="wellness_score">Wellness Score</string>
    <string name="breathing_rate">Breathing Rate</string>
    <string name="heart_rate">Heart Rate</string>
    <string name="prq">PRQ</string>
    <string name="oxygen_saturation">Oxygen Saturation</string>
    <string name="blood_pressure">Blood Pressure</string>
    <string name="stress_level">Stress Level</string>
    <string name="recovery_ability">Recovery Ability</string>
    <string name="stress_response">Stress Response</string>
    <string name="hrv_sdnn">HRV-SDNN</string>
    <string name="view_more">View More</string>
    <string name="bpm">bpm</string>
    <string name="brpm">brpm</string>
    <string name="ms">ms</string>
    <string name="moving_or_disruption_identified_msg">Movements or other disruptions were identified. Try again, looking directly into the camera without moving until the measurement is complete.</string>
    <!--    face detect bottom sheet   -->
    <string name="face_not_detected">Face not detected</string>
    <string name="face_not_detected_msg">Please point the camera to your face and make sure you are not too far or too close.</string>
    <string name="face_scanning_msg">Please stay still and avoid unnecessary movements until face detection is complete.</string>
    <string name="stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="error_message">Error (%d)</string>
    <string name="warning_message_1">Warning (%s)</string>
    <string name="ok">Ok</string>
    <string name="no_finger_detected">Place your finger on the rear camera</string>
    <string name="finger_scan_hint">Place your finger on the rear camera (not on the selfie camera).</string>
    <string name="finger_scanning_msg">Make sure that your finger completely covers the camera.</string>
    <string name="feedback_form">Feedback Form</string>
    <string name="rate_your_experience_with">Rate your experience with</string>
    <string name="feedback_title">Feedback Title</string>
    <string name="ex_works_beautifully">Ex. Works Beautifully!</string>
    <string name="write_your_feedback">Write Your Feedback</string>
    <string name="type_your_feedback_here">Type Your Feedback Here</string>
    <string name="pls_enter_feedback_title">Please enter feedback title</string>
    <string name="pls_enter_feedback">Please enter feedback</string>
    <string name="high">High</string>
    <string name="medium">Medium</string>
    <string name="normal">Normal</string>
    <string name="low">Low</string>

    <string name="orientation_not_supported">Unsupported orientation. Return to portrait mode</string>
    <string name="change_session_mode_error">Failed changing mode. Try again</string>
    <string name="frames_lost_face_error">Try again, making sure to look straight into the camera without moving until the measurement is complete.</string>
    <string name="frames_lost_finger_error">Try again, making sure not to remove your finger from the camera until the measurement is complete.</string>
    <string name="frames_lost_warning">Could not collect enough data during the last few seconds. Please try not to move.</string>
    <string name="face_reset_error">Movements or other disruptions were identified. Try again, looking directly into the camera without moving until the measurement is complete.</string>
    <string name="finger_reset_error">Movements or other disruptions were identified. Try again, making sure that your finger is completely covering the camera, and that you do not move until the measurement is complete.</string>
    <string name="reset_warning">Could not collect data for over one second. Please try not to move.</string>
    <string name="low_battery_error">Required battery level : 20%</string>
    <string name="cannot_start_session">Cannot start measurement.</string>
    <string name="face_not_detected_error">Your face was not detected for the minimum time required to start measuring. please try again.</string>
    <!--    <string name="finger_not_detected_error">Your finger was not detected for the minimum time required to start measuring. please try again.</string>-->
    <string name="finger_not_detected_error">Place your finger on the rear camera. (Not on the front/selfie camera)</string>
    <string name="license_activation_failed">Licensing error, please contact customer support.</string>
    <string name="torch_shut_down">Torch shut down during measurement</string>
    <string name="error_warning">Error/Warning</string>
    <string name="measurement_results">Measurement Results</string>
    <string name="wellness_msg">The measured indicators are not intended for medical use</string>
    <string name="vital_signs">Vital Signs</string>
    <string name="blood">Blood</string>
    <string name="energy">Energy</string>
    <string name="heart_rate_variability">Heart Rate Variability</string>
    <string name="learn_more">Learn More</string>
    <string name="view_your_abnormal_results"> View Your Abnormal Results</string>
    <string name="your_abnormal_results">Your Abnormal results</string>
    <string name="delete_result">Delete Result</string>
    <string name="are_you_sure_want_to_delete_measurement">Are you sure you want to delete this measurement?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="heart_rate_msg_1">This is the number of times your heart beats per minute. The normal resting rate is 60 to 100 beats for a healthy adult.</string>
    <string name="heart_rate_msg_2">Think of your heart as a pump that pushes blood through your body. With every beat, the heart pumps blood containing oxygen and nutrients around the body and brings back waste products. A healthy heart supplies the body with the right amount of blood at a rate proportionate to whatever activity the body is undertaking.
\n\n
Normal resting rates can differ between people. Furthermore, heart rates are lower when at rest and increase during exercise. Moreover, this rate can change with different situations such as the weather, body position, emotions, body size, medication, and  participate in athletics.
\n\n
Tracking Heart Rate can provide insight into fitness levels, heart health, and emotional health. Moreover, for individuals taking medication for cardiovascular conditions, daily Heart Rate measurements can assist the doctor in advising on the proper course of treatment.
\n\n
A healthy heartbeat is important in protecting cardiac health. If you feel that your heart is beating out of rhythm (too fast or too slow), speak to a doctor about your symptoms.</string>
    <string name="hrv_sdnn_msg_1">SDNN is a calculated parameter of Heart Rate Variability (HRV) that represents the standard deviation of normal-to-normal R-R-intervals. SDNN is expressed in milliseconds, and a normal value for this is over 50. However, SDNN values are also dependent on age and gender and normally get lower with age.
\n\n
An individual\'s heartbeats do not occur at constant intervals, but rather with a small variance between them. HRV measures the variation in time between the heartbeats.</string>
    <string name="hrv_sdnn_msg_2">High levels of HRV generally indicate aerobic and general fitness. Athletes may track HRV to adjust their training program. They can learn when the body is being overworked, which often results in a drop in HRV, and can learn how fast they recover. Moreover, persons with high HRV may be more resilient to stress.
\n\n
HRV measurements provide feedback about your lifestyle and can help inspire taking steps toward a healthier life. If you are implementing changes in your lifestyle such as meditation, better sleep, better nutrition, and participation in sports and physical activity, you may notice changes in the HRV. In addition, this could help to track your nervous system\'s reactions to the environment, emotions, thoughts, and feelings.
\n\n
The sympathetic system (Stress Response) is activated when the body is under stress, causing the heart to beat faster and more regularly, and causing HRV to decrease. The parasympathetic system (Recovery Ability) manages the heart\'s activity to help the body reach a relaxed state and to recover from a stressful event. This relaxation response results in a slower and less regular heartbeat and is indicated by a higher HRV.

If you have questions about your results, seek a doctor\'s advice and they will let you know what\'s normal for your specific condition.</string>
    <string name="stress_level_msg_1">Stress is the body\'s reaction to a challenge or demand. There are five levels of Stress:</string>
    <string name="stress_level_msg_2">The human body is designed to experience stress
and react to it. When you deal with challenges and changes, your body produces physical and mental responses. Stress might be positive, keeping us alert, motivated, and ready to avoid danger. However, stress becomes a problem when stressors continue without relief or periods of relaxation.
\n\n
The application\'s Stress Level measurement is based on Baevsky\'s Stress Index which is approved for use in the US and in Europe. The index is calculated using Heart Rate Variability (HRV) measurements.</string>
    <string name="stress_level_msg_3">It\'s important to note that Stress Levels are indicative only and need to be corroborated with other parameters by a doctor before making a valid diagnosis. Stress Levels are highly dynamic and should be monitored over longer periods to detect abnormal trends.</string>
    <string name="recovery_ability_msg_1">The Recovery Ability that is also known as "rest and digest" response refers to the body\'s ability to recover, accumulate energy, and regulate bodily functions after stressful occurrences. This is part of the autonomic system that consists of two sub-systems, the sympathetic (Stress Response) system and the parasympathetic (Recovery Ability) system. Your Heart Rate Variability is reflected in the balance between these two sub-systems.
\n\n
There are three zones of Recovery Ability:</string>
    <string name="recovery_ability_msg_2">The normal and high zones are more desirable than the low zone. In the normal and high zones, the body is able to effectively conserve energy, relax, or recover from a stressful occurrence.
\n\n
The parasympathetic metric measures the activity of the PNS and indicates how capable a person is of relaxing or recovering after stressful events. A low zone would indicate a stressful state, while a high zone would suggest calmness.
\n\n
The system plays an important role in alleviating stress and promoting recovery. It does so by inhibiting the activity of the sympathetic nervous system and ceasing the production of stress hormones. It returns bodily functions to their resting state by slowing the heart rate, lowering blood pressure, reducing muscle tension, and restoring regular breathing, digestion, and glandular activity.
\n\n
The Recovery Ability is derived from the parasympathetic nervous system (PNS) index.
The PNS Index calculation is based on the following three parameters: Mean RRI, RMSSD, and SD1.
\n\n
These zones should be used as a guide only. Seek a doctor\'s advice in order to obtain a valid diagnosis.</string>
    <string name="stress_response_msg_1">The Stress Response, which is also known as "fight or flight" response, refers to a physiological reaction to imminent danger that occurs when we are scared, anxious, stressed, attacked, or threatened. Essentially, it prepares our body to either deal with a threat or to run for safety. This is part of the autonomic system that consists of two sub-systems, the sympathetic (Stress Response) system and the parasympathetic (recovery ability) system. Your Heart Rate Variability is reflected in the balance between those two sub-systems.
\n\n
There are three zones of Stress Response:</string>
    <string name="stress_response_msg_2">The normal and low zones are more desirable than the high zone. In the normal and low zones, the body is able to effectively respond to stressful situations and emergencies.
\n\n
When preparing for an emergency, the sympathetic nervous system (SNS) activates numerous complex pathways and components. These physiological activities help to achieve a faster heart rate, breathing rate, and blood pressure. Noticeable changes include blood flow that moves away from the skin and stomach, and is redirected from the intestines to the brain, heart, and muscles, as well as sweating, "goose-bumps", dilation of the pupils, and a host of other feelings that appear during the Stress Response. In addition, there is a psychological aspect to the Stress Response. Automated responses include quick thinking and focusing on salient targets such as the source of the threat and escape options.
\n\n
The stress created by a situation is helpful and increases the chances of coping effectively with the threat. This type of stress can help you perform better in situations where you are under pressure to do well.
\n\n
This Stress Response is derived from the sympathetic nervous system (SNS) Index. The SNS Index is calculated based on the following three parameters: Heart Rate, Baevsky\'s Stress Index, and SD2.
\n\n
These zones should be used as a guide only. Seek a doctor\'s advice in order to obtain a valid diagnosis.</string>
    <string name="oxygen_saturation_msg_1">Oxygen Saturation, or SpO2, is a measure of how much oxygen the red blood cells are carrying from the lungs to the rest of the body. Normal SpO2 for healthy lungs ranges between 95%-100%. For individuals with chronic conditions or lung diseases could be lower than 95%.</string>
    <string name="oxygen_saturation_msg_2">A low level of oxygen in the blood is called hypoxemia. Typically, an Oxygen Saturation level lower than 90% is considered hypoxemia, which can be caused by chronic pulmonary diseases (COPD, COVID-19, Asthma, Lung Fibrosis, pulmonary hypertension), heart failure, sleep apnea, anemia, and high-altitude exposure (insufficient oxygen in the air) and medications that suppress breathing control.
\n\n
Common symptoms of hypoxemia include headache, rapid heart rate, coughing, shortness of breath, wheezing, confusion, and blueness of the skin and mucus membranes (cyanosis). Oxygen Saturation levels can also be used by athletes to understand whether a decrease in performance is a result of altitude changes or ability.
\n\n
If you feel that your Oxygen Saturation is low, speak to a doctor about your symptoms. They
will let you know what is normal for your specific condition.</string>
    <string name="prq_msg_1">The Pulse-Respiration Quotient (PRQ) indicates the state of cardiorespiratory activity. The normal quotient range is 4 to 5. PRQ readings are affected by one\'s age, sex, physiological constitution, physical activity, psychophysical and cognitive activity, body posture, environmental influences, and state of health.
\n\n
The PRQ is calculated by dividing the Heart Rate by the Breathing Rate. It provides additional knowledge that cannot be obtained when analyzing the Heart Rate and the Breathing Rate separately.</string>
    <string name="prq_msg_2">The Pulse-Respiration Quotient (PRQ) reflects emergent properties of the complex interplay between cardiac and respiratory activities. The pulse-respiration quotient metric measures to what extent this interplay is functioning normally. A low or high score would indicate that your HR and/or BR are working disproportionately, which may indicate that both the heart and the lungs are working inefficiently. Moreover, a person\'s pathophysiological state (the functional changes associated with or resulting from disease or injury) is indicated by abnormal PRQ readings.
\n\n
These results should be used as a guide only. Seek doctor\'s advice in order to obtain a valid diagnosis.</string>
    <string name="breath_rate_msg_1">The number of breaths you take per minute. The normal at-rest Breathing Rate is 12 to 20 breaths per minute for a healthy adult. In general, breathing rates are slightly faster in women than men.</string>
    <string name="breath_rate_msg_2">When you inhale, oxygen enters your lungs and circulates to the various internal organs. When you exhale, carbon dioxide moves out of the body. A normal Breathing Rate plays a critical role in keeping the balance of oxygen and carbon dioxide even in the body. If the oxygen level in the blood is low, or if the carbon dioxide level in the blood is high, your Breathing Rate increases.
\n\n
Various factors affect the Breathing Rate, including injuries, exercise, fever, anxiety, emotions, mood, alcohol, medication, metabolic issues, and medical conditions. A high or low rate might be the result of an activity, and therefore does not indicate that there is anything wrong. However, in other cases, such as various diseases, injuries, dehydration or heart problems, a change in the Breathing Rate may occur that can be considered abnormal, thereby necessitating medical attention.
\n\n
Knowing your Breathing Rate can help your doctor provide you with medical advice. If your Breathing Rate changes or if you feel that your breathing is too fast or too slow, speak to a doctor about your symptoms.</string>
    <string name="blood_pressure_msg_1">The pressure of blood exerted on the walls of the arteries, which carry blood from the heart to other parts of the body. Normal systolic pressure is from
100 to 129.</string>
    <string name="blood_pressure_msg_2">Blood Pressure measures the pressure of circulating blood against artery walls, and it is measured by two numbers. The first number, or systolic pressure, refers to the pressure inside the artery when the heart contracts and pumps blood throughout the body. The second number, or diastolic pressure, refers to the pressure inside the artery when the heart is at rest and is filling with blood.
\n\n
Most people don\'t know if they have high Blood Pressure - especially since there may be no noticeable warning signs or symptoms - and therefore the Blood Pressure must be measured. Blood Pressure changes in response to different activities and is recommended to be measured while at rest. Consistently high blood pressure readings may result in a diagnosis of high blood pressure (hypertension), which poses a higher risk for health problems such as heart disease, heart attack, and stroke. In most cases, high blood pressure has no defined cause, and it is called primary hypertension. However, it is related to unhealthy lifestyles such as physical inactivity, stressful life, obesity, shift work, pregnancy, etc. It should be emphasized that Blood Pressure can be managed through diagnosis, lifestyle changes, medication and long-term monitoring.
\n\n
Blood Pressure is categorized as low, normal, or elevated: low blood pressure is defined as systolic pressure of less than 100, normal blood pressure is defined as systolic pressure of 100 to 129, while elevated blood pressure is defined as systolic pressure of 130 or higher.
\n\nThese numbers should be used as a guide only. A single Blood Pressure measurement that is higher than normal is not necessarily an indication of a problem. Your doctor will want to see multiple Blood Pressure measurements over several days or weeks before making a diagnosis of high blood pressure and commencing treatment.</string>
    <string name="reading_name_title_msg">Your %s is %s</string>
    <string name="reading_not_recorded_msg">%s is not recorded</string>
    <string name="no_enough_data_was_recorded">Not enough data was recorded to calculate a valid result.</string>
    <string name="could_not_collect_data_over_seconds">Could not collect data for over 0.5 seconds.</string>
    <string name="pls_dont_remove_your_finger">Please do not move your finger</string>
    <string name="required_permission_not_granted">Required permission not granted</string>
    <string name="blood_test">Blood Test</string>
    <string name="my_plan">My Plan</string>
    <string name="payment_history">Payment History</string>
    <string name="no_plan_title">You don\'t have  any subscriptions yet</string>
    <string name="no_plan_msg">To continue scanning\n please buy a plan</string>
    <string name="subscribe_now">Subscribe Now</string>
    <string name="you_have_value_free_scans_now">You have %d free health\nscans now!</string>
    <string name="purchase_subscription_now_for_unlimited_scans">Purchase a subscription now\nfor unlimited health scans.</string>
    <string name="continue_scan">Continue Scan</string>
    <string name="your_value_free_scans_expired">Your %d free health scans\nhave expired!</string>
    <string name="your_plan_is_about_to_expire">Your plan is about to expire.</string>
    <string name="renew_your_subscription_for_unlimited_scans">Please renew your subscription\nfor unlimited health scans.</string>
    <string name="renew_now">Renew Now</string>
    <string name="subscriptions_plan">Subscriptions Plan</string>
    <string name="choose_your_plan">Choose your Plan</string>
    <string name="choose_the_plan_right_for_you">Choose the plan that\'s right for you.</string>
    <string name="more_information">More Information</string>
    <string name="more_information_msg_1">Payment will be charged to your Account at confirmation of purchase.</string>
    <string name="more_information_msg_2">Subscription automatically renews unless auto-renew is turned off at least 24-hours before the end of the current period.</string>
    <string name="payment_status_success_title">Payment Successful</string>
    <string name="payment_status_success_msg">Your payment has been successfully processed! Details of transaction are included below.</string>
    <string name="payment_status_fail_title">Payment Failed</string>
    <string name="payment_status_fail_msg">We\'re sorry, your payment couldn\'t be processed at this time.</string>
    <string name="payment_status">Payment Status</string>
    <string name="pls_select_plan">Please select Plan</string>
    <string name="retry_payment">Retry Payment</string>
    <string name="plan_expire_date">Plan Expire Date</string>
    <string name="transaction_date">Transaction Date</string>
    <string name="transaction_number">Transaction Number</string>
    <string name="your_plan_is_expired">Your Plan is Expired</string>
    <string name="purchased_on">Purchased on %s</string>
    <string name="payment_details">Payment Details</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="need_to_update_your_plan_not_to_worry_you_can_click_on_the_upgrade_now_button_below">Need to update your plan? Not to worry, you can click on the ‘Upgrade Now’ button below.</string>
    <string name="upcoming_plan">Upcoming Plan</string>
    <string name="successful">Successful</string>
    <string name="view_payment_details">View Payment Details</string>
    <string name="upgrade_now">Upgrade Now</string>
    <string name="no_payment_data_found">No Payment Data Found</string>
    <string name="_1">1</string>
    <string name="_2">2</string>
    <string name="_3">3</string>
    <string name="_4">4</string>
    <string name="_5">5</string>
    <string name="_6">6</string>
    <string name="_7">7</string>
    <string name="_8">8</string>
    <string name="_9">9</string>
    <string name="_10">10</string>
    <string name="wellness_score_msg_1">The Wellness Score is a prediction risk score that is used to predict a person\'s cardiovascular risk for the next 5 to 10 years. The Wellness Score is based on the vital signs measured by Binah\'s technology, and is designed to serve as a reference when measured at rest, under similar conditions during all of the measurements, and if the score is consistent in repeated measurements over time.\n\nThe higher the wellness score, the lower the cardiovascular risk.\n\nHow is it calculated?\nYour Wellness Score is calculated using your vitals results from any single measurement. The values of each one of the vital sign measurements affect your Wellness Score prediction.\nGenerally, a lower Heart Rate at rest implies more efficient heart function and better cardiovascular fitness. Therefore, a higher Heart Rate reduces your Wellness Score - even when the heart rate is within the normal range. For example, heart rates that are higher than 65 reduce the wellness score to a medium score, and values that are higher than 84 reduce the wellness score to a low score.\n\nHRV measures the variation in time between heartbeats. The Stress Level that is calculated from this variance also affects your Wellness Score. Thus. Very High and High stress levels are correlated with a low score, while Mild and Normal stress levels are correlated with a medium score.</string>
    <string name="wellness_score_msg_2">Your Oxygen Saturation level measures the amount of oxygen in the blood delivered from the lungs to the rest of the body. A higher level implies a more efficient function, thus, a lower Oxygen Saturation level reduces the Wellness Score.\n\nIn addition, High Blood Pressure readings at rest may pose a higher risk of health problems and therefore may reduce the Wellness Score.\n\nLearn more at: %s</string>
    <string name="measurement_not_completed_msg">Measurement is not completed, Are you sure want to stop?</string>
    <string name="_0">0</string>
    <string name="sit_still_during_the_measurement">Sit still during the measurement.</string>
    <string name="avoid_moving_or_talk">Avoid moving or talking.</string>
    <string name="stay_focused_on_screen">Stay focused on the screen.</string>
    <string name="wait_until_end_for_best_result">Wait until the end for the best results.</string>
    <string name="normal_prq_range">Normal PRQ range is 4 to 5.</string>
    <string name="normal_resting_heart_rate">Normal resting heart rate is 60 to 100 bpm.</string>
    <string name="tracking_heart_rate_provide">Tracking heart rate can provide insight into fitness levels.</string>
    <string name="athletes_may_track_hrv">Athletes may track HRV to optimise their training program.</string>
    <string name="high_levels_of_hrv">High levels of HRV generally indicate aerobic and general fitness.</string>
    <string name="hold_on_all_the_result_will_appear">Hold on, all the results will appear in a few seconds.</string>
    <string name="symptoms_of_hypoxemia_include_wheezing">Symptoms of hypoxemia include wheezing and confusion.</string>
    <string name="prq_is_calculate_by_dividing_heart_rate">PRQ is calculated by dividing the Heart Rate by the Breathing Rate.</string>
    <string name="make_sure_that_your_finger_completely_covers_the_camera">Make sure that your finger completely covers the camera</string>
    <string name="high_blood_pressure_may_exist_wth_no_noticeable">High blood pressure may exist with no noticeable warning signs.</string>
    <string name="normal_prq_is_4_to_5">Normal PRQ is 4 to 5.</string>
    <string name="try_again">Try Again</string>
    <string name="low_power_mode_title">You are in low power mode</string>
    <string name="low_power_mode_msg">Please turn off low power mode in order to start a new measurement.</string>
    <string name="low_battery_msg">Please charge battery in order to start a new measurement.</string>
    <string name="no_limit_for_scan">No Limit for Scan</string>
    <string name="you_save_value">You save %s</string>
    <string name="type_plan">%s Plan</string>
    <string name="face_or_finger_not_detected_2_times_msg">The face or finger was not detected for a period of over 0.5 second more than 2 times</string>
    <string name="our_company_located_in_ede_the_netherlands_has_a_mission_to_make_social_and_technological_innovations_available_for_healthcare_both_for_professionals_and_patients_as_well_we_consider_that_as_crucial_to_keep_healthcare_qualitative_accessible_and_affordable_our_core_values_are_transparency_integrity_and_human_first">Our company, located in Ede, The Netherlands, has a mission to make social and technological innovations available for healthcare. Both for professionals and patients as well. We consider that as crucial to keep healthcare qualitative, accessible and affordable. Our core values are transparency, integrity and human first.</string>
</resources>